

PROFILE

I have a two years work experience as an IT. I have been specializing in fullstack web development at Becode by taking a 7-month intensive course. After having a great journey of my 2-month internship in Ubigreat, Now I am looking for a job as a fullstack developer.

EDUCATION

FRONT END DEVELOPER INTERNSHIP Ubigreat BV,

Aug 2022- Oct 2022, Brussles, Belgium. Develop, design and test components in a mobile app using ReactNative library.

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT Becode.

Feb 2022 - Present, Liege, Belgium. Project 1: DJ Angerone musician website, It is a website I developed with my team. Java script SASS and HTML are technologies used Project 2: forum website, with Reactjs and Laravel

BACHELOR DEGREE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Eritrea Institute Of Technology,

2012 - 2017, Mai Nefhi, Eritrea.

HARD SKILL

Mysql

ReactJs and ReactNative, SASS, Bootstrap Laravel, ASP.NET, Django, Github, Trello, Vscode, Visual studio DotNet, java, python and JavaScript.

ABIEL KIFLU

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

0456358676



Rue De France 70, Verviers 4800



对 abiel.kiflu.weldegmail.com

https://github.com/AbielKiflu

EXPERIENCES

TRANSLATOR

Brussels Onthaal,

Nov 2020 - Oct 2021, Brussels, Belgium Translate between Tigrina and English

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATION AND MAINTENANCE (IT)

Hidri Distribution company,

Nov 2017 - Sep 2019, Asmara, Eritrea Maintain software's and hardware's. Windows server, odoo framework customization.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

INTERNSHIP

Eritrea Institute Of Technology,

Jun 2017- Aug 2017, Mai Nefhi, Eritrea. php fullstack web development.

SOFT SKILL

Communication Team-Working Problem Solving

LANGUAGES

Tigrina - Mother language English - C1

French - A1

HACKATHON

ICT4Anxiety

Smart city Charleroi